dashbid.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy — DashBid | Programmatic Advertising That Works

DashBid is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users and customers. This Privacy Policy statement explains the data usage practices of our web site. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us by e-mail at support@DashBid.com.

 **Privacy Policy Statement**

This website uses Google Analytics and other data services to help analyze how visitor use this site. Google Analytics and other services uses “cookies”, which are small text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. No personally identifiable information is collected about you unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on this website.

The anonymous information generated by Google Analytics and other cookies about your use of this website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google and other services. This information is then processed to compile statistical reports on website activity for DashBid.com. We use these reports to evaluate aggregate visitor usage so that we can optimize the content, and its marketing, to better meet your needs.

This site uses retargeting from Google, Rubicon and Adroll. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. First-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) are used together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website.

Visitors can opt-out of our partners’ targeted display advertising on <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>, and to opt-out from Facebook ads use <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/cookies>.

All rights reserved. No part of our website may be reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic or mechanical, including photocopying, recording, or by any information storage and retrieval system, without permission in writing from the DashBid offices.
